### Vimal Arockia Raj W

Graphics/UI Designer





ttps://arockrockz.github.io/portfolio/

#### **SUMMARY**

UI Designer with 2 years of professional IT experience with knowledge in web technologies. To Be a Successful professional in a Globally Respected Company and to achieve the objectives of the company with Honesty and Fairness and to Continuously Upgrade MyKnowledge and Skills.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

HTML css Bootstrap Javascript Photoshop Illustrator Prototype development

### **PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE**

- ✓ Six Month of experience in PPV Technology (P) LTD as Hardware Engineer from February 2018 to July 2018.
- ✓ Eight Month of experience in Fusion Cloud IIc as Senior Designer from August 2018 to April 2019.
- ✓ One Year and Nine Months of experience in Mukesh Infoserve Pvt, Ltd, as UI Designer from June 2019 to March 2021.

### **SKILL SET**

LANGUAGES : HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript

**TOOLS**: Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio, Spring Boot

**DESIGN**: Photoshop, Illustrator, Just in Mind

**OS** : Windows XP, 7,8,10

**AREA OF INTEREST**: Web Designing, Hardware, Photoshop

**PERSONAL SKILLS**: Interpersonal skills, Quick understand, Adaptable person.

**HOBBIES** : Playing carom, Surfing internet, Listen music.

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# 1. UI Design Roofing Concern, 2019-Present

- Designed ERP For Roofing Concern, For their Purchase, Sales, and Inventory.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.

# 3. UI Design Digital Signage, 2019-Present

- Designed Web Poral For Furniture Concern.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Designed Mobile App For whole Seller Using Just In Mind Tool

# 2. UI Design Fabric And Clothing Industry, 2019-Present

- Designed Purchase Portal For Fabric Concern.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Developed Admin Poral Design For 21 Pages.

# 4. UI Design GRPO Portal, 2019-Present

- Designed GRPO Poral For VKC.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Developed Admin Poral Design For 21 Pages.
- Designed Mobile App For whole Seller Using Just In Mind Tool

### UI Design Gold Jewellery ERP Portal, 2019-Present

- Designed ERP Web Poral For Gold Jewellery.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Developed Admin Poral Design For 520 Pages.

- 6. UI Design
  EEB Bank Admin Portal, 2020-Present
- Designed ERP Web Poral For Bank.
- Developed Prototype for All Pages Using Just In Mind Prototyping Tool.
- Developed Designed Page Using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Developed Admin Poral Design For 15 Pages.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Branch:** COMPUTER SCIENCE

COURSE	INSTITUTION	BOARD OF EXAMINATION	YEAR OF PASSING	PERCENTAGE OBTAINED
B.E	RVS College Of Engineering ,Dindigul-5.	Anna University	2016	6.2 CGPA
HSC	S.M.B Matric Hr.Sec School,Dindigul-5	State Board	2012	62%
SSLC	S.M.B Matric Hr.Sec School,Dindigul-5	Matriculation	2010	71.4%

### **PROJECTS & WORKSHOPS**

- ✓ Developed Mini-project on photo studio using PHP
- ✓ Developed Mini-project on vehicle online tracking using PHP
- ✓ Developed final year project on a novel approach to enhance image quality by super resolution using java
- ✓ Attended Inplant training on PHP for 2days at UNIQ technologies
- ✓ Attended Internship training on PHP for 5days at UNIQ technologies
- ✓ Attended workshop on ANDROID APP DEVELOPEMENT
- ✓ Attended workshop on ANTENNA MODELLING AND DESIGNING

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

NAME : Vimal Arockia Raj.W

**DATE OF BIRTH** : 21-01-1995

GENDER : Male
MARITAL STATUS : Single

LANGUAGES KNOWN : English, Tamil (Read, Speak, Write)

FATHER'S NAME : Wilson.A (Late)

MOTHER'S NAME : Caroline Dorathy.M

PERMANENT ADDRESS : 24/64, Y.M.R patty, Opp Aarthi Grand Ciniplex,

Dindigul-624001.

I hereby declare that above furnished particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Dindigul

Date: SIGNATURE